<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="77">
    <author>tn4799, RickBlackLabele</author>
    <version>2.1.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Speed Camera</en>
        <de>Blitzer</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[A speed camera that triggers at about 50km/h.
There is a small tolerance range for speed measurement to prevent measurement inaccuracies.
If you drive too fast while passing the speed camera you will be flashed and have to pay a fine.
The speed camera works in both directions.
One speed camera initally costs 150000$. After that the daily upkeep is 1000$.

When placing the speed camera a dialog shows up to allow the configuration of the speed limit of the speed camera.

Changelog:
v1.1.0.0
 - Fixed a bug with loading values from the placeables.xml.
 - Added blinking warning translation so other speed cameras can use the translation if they have enabled this feature.
 - Added an option so that the owner of the speed camera gains the money of the fine minus a little transaction fee.

v2.0.0.0
 - Added a dialog to configure the values of the speed camera yourself on placement.

v2.1.0.0
 - Added possibility to allow placement on non-buyable farmland
 - Added possibility to reconfigure the speed camera post placement. To do so you have to stand near the speed camera and then press the activate key
]]></en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Ein Blitzer, der bei ca. 50km/h auslöst.
Es gibt einen kleinen Toleranzbereich bei der Geschwindigkeitsmessung um Messungenauigkeiten vorzubeugen.
Wenn man zu schnell ist, während man am Blitzer vorbeifährt, wird man geblitzt und es wird eine Geldstrafe erhoben.
Der Blitzer funktioniert in beide Fahrtrichtungen.
Ein Blitzer kostet 150000€ in der Anschaffung und anschließend 1000€/Tag Unterhaltskosten.

Beim Platzieren des Blitzers erscheint ein Dialog, mit dem man einstellen kann ab welcher Geschwindigkeit der Blitzer ausgelöst wird.

Changelog:
v1.1.0.0
 - Bug beim Laden der Werte aus der Placeables.xml gefixt.
 - Blinking Warning Übersetzung Eingefügt damit andere Blitzer die Übersetzung haben sollten Sie diese die Option nutzen.
 - Option hinzugefügt damit der Besitzer des Blitzers die Strafzahlung bekommt abzüglich einer Transaktionsgebühr.

v2.0.0.0
 - Dialog zum Einstellen der Werte des Blitzers beim Platzieren hinzugefügt

v2.1.0.0
 - Möglichkeit hinzugefügt, den Blitzer auf nicht kaufbarem Land zu platzieren
 - Möglichkeit hinzugefügt, den Blitzer nach dem Platzieren neu zu konfigurieren. Hierfür muss man zum Blitzer gehen und dann die Aktivieren-Taste drücken
]]></de>
    </description>

	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>

    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/SC_PayFineEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="src/SpeedCameraValuesConfiguredEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="src/gui/PlacementDialog.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="src/registerDialog.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="src/placeOnNonbuyableFarmland.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

	<placeableSpecializations>
		<specialization name="placeableSpeedCamera" className="PlaceableSpeedCamera" filename="src/PlaceableSpeedCamera.lua"/>
	</placeableSpecializations>

	<placeableTypes>
		<type name="speedCamera" parent="simplePlaceable" filename="$dataS/scripts/placeables/Placeable.lua">
			<specialization name="placeableSpeedCamera" />
			<specialization name="infoTrigger"/>
		</type>
	</placeableTypes>

	<storeItems>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="speedCamera.xml"/>
	</storeItems>

    <l10n>
		<text name="storeItem_speedCamera">
			<en>Speed Camera 50km/</en>
			<de>Blitzer 50km/h</de>
		</text>
		<text name="function_speedCamera">
			<en>If you drive too fast past the speed camera, you will be flashed and have to pay a fine.</en>
			<de>Wenn man zu schnell am Blitzer vorbeifährt wird man geblitzt und muss eine Geldstrafe bezahlen.</de>
		</text>
		<text name="Notification_speedCamera">
			<!-- Info:
				%d is used for the amount of money that has to be paid  filename="$dataS/scripts/placeables/Placeable.lua"
				%s is used to add the currency symbol to the text

				Of course a own text is possible but please use %d and %s in your text
			-->
			<en>%d%s for driving to fast</en>
			<de>%d%s für zu schnelles Fahren</de>
		</text>
		<!-- only needed if you want a blinking warning.-->
		<text name="warning_speedCamera">
            <en>You driven %d mph to fast</en>
            <de>Du bist %d km/h zu schnell gefahren</de>
        </text>

		<!--Translations for placement dialog-->
		<text name="dialog_speedCamera_title">
			<en>Speed Camera Configuration</en>
			<de>Blitzereinstellungen</de>
		</text>

		<text name="dialog_speedLimit_text">
			<en>Speed Limit</en>
			<de>Tempolimit</de>
		</text>

		<text name="dialog_ownerGetsMoney_text">
			<en>Owner receives Money</en>
			<de>Besitzer bekommt Geld</de>
		</text>

		<text name="dialog_error_invalidSpeedLimit">
			<en>The speed limit has to be greater than 0.</en>
			<de>Das Tempolimit muss größer als 0 sein.</de>
		</text>

		<text name="dialog_error_notANumber">
			<en>The speed limit has to be a Number greater than 0.</en>
			<de>Das Tempolimit muss eine Zahl größer als 0 sein.</de>
		</text>

		<text name="action_openDialog">
			<en>Open configuration dialog</en>
			<de>Konfigurationsdialog öffnen</de>
		</text>
	</l10n>
</modDesc>
